

igypap@gmail.com



+48 504 781 817

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- JAVA
- Spring
- SQL
- Maven
- Docker

SECTORS

- Financial
- · Derivatives Market
- Consulting
- Insurance

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATES

- Master's Degree in Electrical Engineering at Kielce University of Technology
- Bachelor Degree in Electrical Engineering at Kielce University of Technology

LANGUAGES

- Polish
- English

Igor Paprzycki

Senior Java developer / Technical Lead

Profile

Igor is Senior Java developer with overall of 11 years of experience in the area related to software development.

He has demonstrated proficiency in leading teams through the integration of reusable components, designing and developing generic application components in microservices architecture, and contributing to the creation of a data streaming platform for Risk Management Services.

Igor's extensive experience includes stakeholder interaction throughout the software lifecycle, from design and development to release and support.

Project experience

PWC - JULY 2021 - PRESENT

Played a leading technical role in the technical domain, overseeing a project focused on integrating reusable components across various clients. Designed and developed generic and reusable application components within a microservices architecture, catering to multiple clients.

Tech stack: JAVA 17, Spring, SQL Server, Docker, Kubernetes, Azure DevOps, NodeJS

CITI BANK - FEBRUARY 2020 - JUNE 2021

Pioneered the development of a data streaming platform using Apache Flink for Risk Management Services, showcasing expertise in cutting-edge technologies.

Tech stack: JAVA, Spring, Apache Kafka, Apache Flink

Pragmasoft / PZU - MAY 2018 - FEBRUARY 2020

Developed a web-based application for claim submission, contributing to the efficiency of microservices infrastructure. Tech stack: **JAVA**, **TypeScript**, **Spring**, **Hibernate**, **Soap**, **PostgreSQL**, **Docker**

Goldman Sachs - JUNE 2017 - APRIL 2018

Design and developed Clearing House communication API for internal trade and clearing processing in the Derivatives market, ensuring seamless and secure transactions.

Tech stack: JAVA, Spring, Apache Kafka, Hibernate, DB2

Previous experience - SINCE 2013

Previous experience includes freelance software development and engineering work related to design and commissioning of a Fan Blade Out facility for aviation engines testing centre.